- Are you sure?
- Look, I grew up on a farm, okay?
(Penny:)From what I heard, they're either having sex
or Howard's caught in a milking machine.
(Penny:)Do you mind if I stay here tonight?
No. Yeah, take the couch, or my bed.
I just got new pillows.
(Leonard:)Hypoallergenic.
(Penny:)Uh, the couch is good.
(Sheldon:)Hold that thought. Leonard, a moment.
(Leonard:)You have a problem with this.
(Sheldon:)Where do I begin?
(Leonard:)It's up to you. Crazy person's choice.
(Sheldon:)Well, first, we don't have house guests.
(Sheldon:)Frankly, if I could afford the rent,
I'd ask you to leave.
(Leonard:)Your friendship means a lot
to me as well. What else?
(Sheldon:)Well, our earthquake supplies.
- We have a two-man, two-day kit.
- So?
So if there's an earthquake
and the three of us are trapped here...
(Sheldon:)...we could be out of food
by tomorrow afternoon.
(Leonard:)Are you suggesting
that if we let Penny stay...
(Leonard:)...we might succumb to cannibalism?